<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on The 2nd Fog Computing&#43; Workshop</title>
    <link>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/fogcomputing/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on The 2nd Fog Computing&#43; Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ntusg-iot.github.io/fogcomputing/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/fogcomputing/home/fogcomputing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/fogcomputing/home/fogcomputing/</guid>
      <description>**The 1st Workshop on LPWAN Systems and Applications** -- The 2nd Fog Computing+ Workshop: Trustworthy Fog SCSE Computer Networks and Communications Lab
Nanyang Technological University (NTU), Singapore
OpenFog Consortium Greater China Region
Date: December 14th, 2018
Venue: Lecture Theatre LT10, North Spine, NTU (Click here to check the map)
Registration: Click here to register online
Menu: The menu of refreshment, lunch and coffee break is available here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/fogcomputing/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/fogcomputing/home/about/</guid>
      <description>About Fog Computing+ Fog computing is an emerging computing paradigm that distributes computing, storage, control and networking functions closer to the “things” along a cloud-to-thing continuum, enabling unprecedented level of intelligence to the physical world. This “Fog Computing+” workshop series, with strong support from the OpenFog Consortium Greater China Region and Nanyang Technological University, aim to bring together leading researchers regularly to discuss fog computing research and innovative applications (i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/fogcomputing/home/cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/fogcomputing/home/cfp/</guid>
      <description>Call for Five-Minute Presentations This year’s workshop will include a number of presentations by research students and staff members. The length of each presentation is 5 minutes plus 2 ~ 3 minutes of Q/A. This session will provide a venue for students to present their existing studies and work in progress to receive feedback from the attendees of the workshop. Interested students and staff members can send the titles, abstracts, short bios to the Session Coordinator at SONG0167@e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/fogcomputing/home/agenda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/fogcomputing/home/agenda/</guid>
      <description>Agenda    &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;      9:30 - 9:45 AM Refreshment   9:45 - 9:50 AM Openning
By Asst Prof Rui Tan   9:50 - 10:40 AM Keynote: Task Scheduling Algorithms in Fog Computing Networks
By Prof Yang Yang (ShanghaiTech University)
Abstract: Fog computing has recently attracted a lot of attentions from communication, computing and control communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/fogcomputing/home/organizers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntusg-iot.github.io/fogcomputing/home/organizers/</guid>
      <description> Organization Committee Workshop Co-Chairs  Rui Tan Yonggang Wen  Honored Organization Committee Members  Wentong Cai Chengzheng Sun  Web Chair  Chaojie Gu  Five-Minute Presentation Coordinator  Qun Song SONG0167@e.ntu.edu.sg  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>